All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World,
Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island,
which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
There, they found themselves facing the new Fishman Pirates,
who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and instigated an all-out war.
At the last moment, the Sea Kings arrived
to stop the Noah from crashing into Fishman Island.
Someone help! I don't know what to do!
You won't stop bleeding!
I'm afraid he's going to die!
You can give him some of my blood!
It's Type F!
Take as much as you need!
Hey, Team Bay!
I would like you...
to join my crew.
The Secret Revealed. The Truth About the Ancient Weapon.
The royal family has reached a decision!
Free! Finally free!
Screw you, Horty! Now who's in chains?
I'm sorry that I was going to be a slave for the rest of my life!
Thank you, straw-heads!
I swear I'll repay you someday,
after I become King of the Pirates!
What? That's a bit ambitious.
Hey, what's wrong with having dreams?
Come on, players! I can set sail for the New World!
Your Majesty! Are you sure it's wise to release Horty's human slaves?
Not to question your judgment!
But the hatred they have for Horty?
They might turn against all Fishmen!
We can't let such fears turn us into something we're not.
This island has always been a welcoming, safe place for pirates to rest.
And these humans never meant us any deliberate harm.
We have no right to imprison them.
Now then, as for the rest of the new Fishmen pirates,
that's a different story!
Ah! Don't cut my head off!
Please spare our lives!
Your Highness! Really!
We didn't know anything about Horty killing the Queen!
They lied to us!
We got duped by a bunch of lunatics!
That's the truth!
It's Horty's fault!
We're not responsible!
Mmm.
Oh!
From here on,
I officially order you all to live here on the main island.
What?!
Hang on!
You're telling us to live law-abiding lives?
It could be a lot worse, better than working for Horty.
Come on! You can't be serious, King!
We don't want them living among us!
We won't feel safe to let our kids walk down the street!
We'll be right back!
To clarify, you will serve your time, of course, and you will work under the supervision of
my army.
I will provide you all with gainful employment to use up all that energy of yours.
And from this day forward, the Fishman District will be sealed off and all entry prohibited!
The dark side of the Fishman had been exposed, along with the true killer of Queen Otohime.
The conspirator, Horty Jones, attempted to seize control of Fishman Island, but he failed.
All thanks to a band of human pirates who happened to be passing through at just the right time.
I'll be right back.
Hey, have you seen Straw Hat Luffy around?
Well, he, um, absconded.
He fled?!
Why did you leave the plaza without saying anything?
Are you running away?
We're not too big on attention.
You saw how many spectators we had watching us fight down there.
If we stick around, they'd just treat us like heroes or some dumb crap.
Just the thought of it makes me want to puke.
But why?
Isn't it a good thing to be the hero of a nation?
Listen up.
I'll spell it out for you.
A man who shares his sake with other people, now that's a hero.
But I want it all for myself.
Keep your damn sake!
And stop putting dumb ideas in her head!
Why won't you join us, D-Bay?
I know you've got adventure in your blood!
Come on!
It'll be the most fun you've ever had, I swear!
He's right!
Crew up with us, boss!
It'd be awesome to have a former warlord with us!
And helpful!
Luffy can take a little break!
I told you, it's impossible for me to join you now.
But I am still grateful.
It is an honor that you asked.
I am certain that it would be the adventure of my life to sail the sea with you all.
But I am afraid I don't have the luxury to indulge in such pleasures.
I have responsibilities that I must fulfill, and I've put them off long enough as it is.
Once I've seen, to my duties, when I'm free from my sworn obligations, I promise I'll set sail and seek you out, no matter where you may be.
And if you haven't changed your mind and still wish for me to become a member of your crew, well, I'll gladly take you up on your offer then, if you see fit to have me.
You better keep that promise!
Whoa, hey!
A man's gotta do what a man's gotta do.
Give him some time, Captain.
He's really taken with Jinbei.
Luffy made it clear you're worth the wait.
So if you need some me time, you got it.
That is very gracious of you.
So what are we doing next?
Where to? A new world, right?
What? You're leaving just like that?
I haven't thanked you properly!
It's not fair!
Why, we've hardly spoken at all!
Okay! It's settled then!
Let's stay at the Mermaid Cafe a whole week!
You got some kind of nosebleed death wish?
Sounds fun, though.
Hey! Hold on!
Who's that?
Looks like he must be a soldier from Neptune's army.
Straw hats! Please wait just a moment!
Okay, Your Majesty. They're right here and listening.
Well done.
Luffy, my friend, why did you leave in such a rush?
I wanted to thank you!
You don't want to be treated like a damn hero!
Yes, I can appreciate that.
But at least let me throw you the banquet that we originally said to enjoy!
Banquet? Sure!
We'll be right there!
I want to eat the meat!
Don't drop the meat!
Please, Nami. How could we possibly refuse a feast?
Yeah! Let's go pick up Pachi and Kami!
And with Neptune's official decree, the Fishman District was sealed off.
As for the fate of Horty, his officers of the new Fishman Pirates and Vander Decken,
they were all locked away within the prison tower.
Go for it, Kraken! Take him far away!
Wadatsumi! You may not fit in our prison cells, but you are forbidden from ever entering this country again!
Did you catch some?
Yes!
Good job, kids! Let's get them prepared and take them up to the palace.
This banquet for the Straw Hats is gonna be a night to remember!
That's for sure!
They'll get their fill of sea monster meat, no doubt.
And we're bringing all the snacks and cakes we can!
Heard they got bottomless stomachs! We better back all of it!
And every cask of sake we've got, they're drinking nothing but the best tonight!
Welcome to the palace, Straw Hats. I'm honored you've chosen to join us, and I'm eager to speak with you during the banquet.
The Long Flounders will be arriving to take you to the hall.
Whoa! Those are some huge rays!
They're flukes.
But I thought he just called them Flounders.
We're under water? It's so dark!
So surreal! They're really letting us in! I'm kinda nervous!
Ew! It's the royal palace! This is nuts!
What the... Hey! Where's the meat?
Look! The heroes have arrived!
Whoa! Look at all the soldiers down there!
You're safe, Fishman Island! Thank you, Straw Hats!
We'll never forget what you did for us!
All the heroes have arrived!
Oh!
Right?
Heroes! Heroes! Heroes! Heroes!
Put up! We aren't anybody's damn heroes!
Just want to eat the meat!
Yeah, and drink all of your sake too!
I saw that coming.
First look at the stage! This way, you see?
Stage?
Ladies and gentlemen!
We'll soon commence with the banquet in celebration of the Straw Hats!
But first, we proudly present the greatest diva of the deep sea,
Maria Napol!
Yes!
Ha ha ha ha!
We'll see you next time!
And her backing band, the Swing Jazz Orchestra!
Wow! She has the voice of an angel! It's wonderful!
Yeah! Seekin' girl!
You're rockin' my soul right out of this world!
Oh yeah!
Now, please welcome our special guest!
Wait, is it?
The Mermaid Café Dancers!
Dance on the bread!
Their beauty has stolen the breath of countless sailors and pirates alike!
Ba-da-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
Oh yeah!
The Mermaid Café Dancers!
Right!
To be continued...
No picture in the world could capture their beauty!
I should have touched the seawater.
Uh-oh.
So good!
Look at the fish!
Katie!
Ishii!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Yes, now we're talking.
It wouldn't be a banquet without it.
Sweet!
Me first, lady!
That's everything I dreamed it would be!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Down here, mermaids!
Oh my, thank you!
Do you care to give a toast before the feast, King?
Well, before we drink, I'd like to take a brief moment to express my humble gratitude.
The Straw Hat Crew.
Without your hands...
Let's dig it!
To peace!
Now, drink them!
I know, I know.
No one cares about the rambling of the sad old...
Hurry up the food already!
Finally!
Eat, eat, sing, drink, be merry!
Yeah!
Hey!
There's plenty more where that came from.
Thank you!
Good thinking!
I'm just getting started!
Ha, ha, ha!
Such a glut!
Come on!
Let's dance, sisters!
Here we go!
Why not?
Let's dance!
Sure!
Not me, I might dance with you.
Who cares, but sure.
Whoa, the jerk!
As far as the eye can see!
Oh, yeah, that's it, baby.
The spot is hit.
I almost forgot how good this sake is.
Huh? Hey, that's right.
You got busted for stealing some, huh?
Come on, now!
That's all ancient history!
No, Mr. Hero, are you okay?
Conniving bastard, why didn't I think of that?
I'm dying too!
Sanji, no!
Don't get so carried away, all right?
Ugh, I'm so over it.
Honestly, why did I even show up?
Why's a big old hairy guy pouting so much?
Honestly, Straw Hat, don't be rude to the king.
Hey, Luffy, up here!
Luffy!
Raise your mug!
You too, you hairy old king!
But first, you will listen as I briefly express my gratitude.
Oh, Father.
Yeah, I know.
Cheers!
Cheers, indeed.
Let's forget the speech.
You guys!
Cheers!
It's quite excellent.
Does it have something to do with the water?
Oh, you're a kind of sewer young lady, aren't you?
Fill her up!
Come on!
Don't look so shocked!
It's empty, isn't it?
That is some real tolerance.
Ooh!
Dance!
Dance on the rims!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Dancing!
Dance on the rims!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Dancing!
Dancing on the rims!
Ah!
Moonfish Mambo!
The party is rocking!
Shitty, shitty, shitty, baby!
The beat is dropping!
DORRE MI!
Come dance with me!
Yeah!
DORRE MI!
Come dance with me, yeah!
Dance!
DORRE MI!
DIXICI!
DROP LLER MI!
YEAH!
HEAH!
HEA!
Hello, pirate girl. You wanted to speak with me?
I apologize, but this seemed like my only chance to get you alone.
What? Now listen here, I'm very flattered, but I swore to love my wife, Otohime, forever.
She might be dead, but I must honor the oath I made.
I'd like to know who Joy Boy is.
Hmm?
Hmm.
I saw it myself, the Poneglyph in the sea forest.
Just who exactly is he apologizing to?
Are you telling me that you can read it?
I'm a survivor of Ohara.
You don't have to tell me anything if you prefer.
No.
I will gladly tell you everything I know.
You've proven yourself trustworthy.
What I know of Joy Boy is that he was a person from above the sea who lived during the time of the hundred-year void.
Which is to say, more than 800 years ago.
The message you read, he wrote to a mermaid princess who lived on this island during that time period.
It is a letter of apology for failing to keep the promise he made to this island.
What promise?
I'm afraid that I don't know the specific details.
But according to the legend, it's said that somebody will come to fulfill it someday on behalf of Joy Boy.
At least that's the story that's been passed down through our royal family.
And we firmly believe that this day will come.
So we've continued to look after the Noah for generations, just as we promised him.
And when the time arrives, the Noah will finally be put to its intended use, whatever that may be.
I see now.
I couldn't help but overhear that the half-destroyed Noah was taken to the sea forest after the battle came to an end today.
By the Sea Kings, that is.
If Joy Boy truly planned to use the Noah, I have to wonder if he had control of the Sea Kings.
No.
It was actually the former mermaid princess who possessed that fearsome power.
That's what I thought.
And now, Shirahoshi has the same ability.
She has, for quite some time.
But it seems that it did not fully awaken until today.
Hmm.
I can't say that I'm terribly pleased.
I know how you feel.
Two years ago, up in Shandora, I read a poneglyph that located one of the ancient weapons.
All signs indicated this very island.
Hmm.
This mermaid princess who lived during the same time as Joy Boy.
She was known by another name as well, wasn't she?
And now, Shirahoshi possesses the same power, so she will come to inherit the same name too.
A terrible thing for a father to hear, but she is the ancient weapon.
Poseidon.
Jinbei reveals several surprises that occurred during the two years the Straw Hats were split up.
After Whitebeard's death, his position as one of the four emperors was filled by an old enemy.
The Navy also underwent a change, with a new leader emerging after a violent struggle.
And while the crew learns of these troubling developments, Caribou planned some trouble of his own.
On the next, One Piece, the Straw Hats stunned, the new fleet admiral of the Navy, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!